<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Connecting Thoughts</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="SIGN_UP_TEXT">New to Connecting Thoughts ? Sign Up</string>


    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password (optional)</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>


    <string name="label_phone_auth">Phone Number Authentication</string>
    <string name="desc_phone_auth">Use a phone number to authenticate with Firebase.</string>

    <string name="label_anonymous_auth">Anonymous Authentication</string>
    <string name="desc_anonymous_auth">Sign in anonymously and then later upgrade to a full Firebase Auth user.</string>

    <string name="label_custom_auth">Custom Authentication</string>
    <string name="desc_custom_auth">Use a custom token signed by your own server to authenticate with Firebase.</string>

    <string name="label_firebase_ui">FirebaseUI Auth</string>
    <string name="desc_firebase_ui">Use the FirebaseUI-Android library to authenticate with Firebase.</string>


    <string name="hint_user_id">User ID</string>
    <string name="get_custom_token">Get Token</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="create_account">Create Account</string>
    <string name="sign_out">Sign Out</string>
    <string name="verify_email">Verify Email</string>

    <string name="loading">Loading…</string>
    <string name="custom_token">Custom Token</string>
    <string name="signed_in">Logged in !</string>
    <string name="signed_out">You are not logged in !</string>
    <string name="token_null">Token: null</string>
    <string name="hint_email">Email</string>
    <string name="hint_password">Password</string>
    <string name="desc_firebase_lockup">Firebase logo and name</string>

    <string name="status_code_sent">Code Sent</string>
    <string name="status_verification_failed">Verification failed</string>
    <string name="status_verification_succeeded">Verification succeeded</string>
    <string name="status_sign_in_failed">Sign-in failed</string>
    <string name="instant_validation">(instant validation)</string>

    <string name="firebase_status_fmt">Firebase User: %s</string>
    <string name="firebase_user_management">Firebase User Management</string>

    <string name="google_status_fmt">Google User: %s</string>
    <string name="google_title_text">Google Sign In</string>

    <string name="facebook_status_fmt">Facebook User: %s</string>
    <string name="facebook_title_text">Facebook Login</string>

    <string name="emailpassword_status_fmt">Email User: %1$s (verified: %2$b)</string>
    <string name="emailpassword_title_text">Email and Password</string>

    <string name="phone_title_text">Phone Number</string>

    <string name="twitter_status_fmt">Twitter User: %s</string>
    <string name="twitter_title_text">Twitter Login</string>

    <string name="firebaseui_status_fmt">Firebase User: %s</string>
    <string name="firebaseui_title_text">FirebaseUI Auth</string>

    <string name="id_fmt">User ID: %s</string>
    <string name="email_fmt">Email: %s</string>







    <string name="PRIVACY_POLICY_TEXT">Connecting thoughts team is the creator of this Privacy Policy operate at connecting thoughts
        (the ‘Application’) ensure our commitment to your privacy vis-à-vis the protection of your priceless information.
        In order to endow you with our uninterrupted use of services, we may collect and, in some circumstances,
        disclose information about you. To enhance better protection of your privacy we provide this notice explaining
        our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.
        If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, you should contact our Customer Support Desk at
        rsonsdevelopers@gmail.com.  OVERVIEW We commit to respecting your online privacy data. We further recognize your need
        for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information (\"Personal Information\")
        you share with us. Information that is considered personal about you by us includes, but is not limited to, your name,
        address, email address or other contact information.  Our application offers multiple services which can be accessed by
        registering with us by providing the following information.  Mobile number; User operated 4-digit passkey; Name; E-mail Address.
        NOTIFICATION OF MODIFICATIONS AND CHANGES TO THE T&amp;C AND PRIVACY POLICY We reserve the right to change the Terms and
        Privacy Policy from time to time as seen fit, without any intimation to you, and your continued use of the application
        will signify your acceptance of any amendment to these terms.  You are therefore advised to re-read the Terms of Service
        and this Privacy Policy on a regular basis. Should it be that you do not accept any of the modifications or amendments
        to the Terms, you may terminate your use of this application immediately.  INFORMATION WE COLLECT Our application’s
        online requisition form requires users to give us contact information (like your name, telephone number and email address).
        As a connecting thoughts member you are required to provide a valid email address at registration and choose a username
        or alias that represents your identity on our application.  In furtherance to this we also collect device specific
        information such as your International Mobile Equipment Identifiers (IMEI) without your intervention.  Certain information,
        such as your name, e-mail addresses, is collected in order to, among other things, verify your identity and for use as
        account numbers in our record system. Email addresses, Geo-locations, Intellectual Property, listings viewed, any
        information entered in the contact us form or any other form displayed on any section of the application are also collected.
        OUR USE OF YOUR INFORMATION Your contact information is also used to contact you when necessary. We use your IP address to
        help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Application. Your IP address is also used to help identify
        you and to gather broad demographic information. Finally, we may use your IP address to help protect our partners and
        ourselves from fraud. We will continue to enhance our security procedures as new technology becomes available.
        We will transfer information about you if we are acquired by or merged with another company. In this event,
        we will notify you by email or by putting a prominent notice on the application before information about you is transferred
        and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.  We may release your personal information to a third-party in order
        comply with a Court Order or other similar legal procedure, or when we believe in good faith that such disclosure is
        necessary to comply with the law; prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss; or investigate or take action
        regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, or violations of Our Terms of Use. We may disclose personally identifiable
        information to parties in compliance with our Copyright Policy as mentioned in the Terms of Use as we in our sole discretion
        believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy,
        or other unlawful activity. In such events, we may disclose name, address, country, phone number, email address and company
        name.  CONFIDENTIALITY You further acknowledge that the Application may contain information which is designated confidential
        by us and that you shall not disclose such information without our prior written consent.  Your information is regarded as
        confidential and therefore will not be divulged to any third party, unless if legally required to do so to the appropriate
        authorities.  We will not sell, share, or rent your personal information to any third party or use your email address for
        unsolicited mail. Any emails sent by us will only be in connection with the provision of agreed services and products.
        OUR DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private
        communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in
        this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting and foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to
        the government, law enforcement agencies or third parties. Under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully
        intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or members may abuse or misuse your information that they
        collect from our Application. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not
        promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications would always
        remain private.  As a matter of policy, we do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any
        third party. However, the following describes some of the ways that your personally identifiable information may be disclosed.
        External Service Providers: There may be a number of services offered by external service providers that help you use our
        Application. If you choose to use these optional services, and in the course of doing so, disclose information to the external
        service providers, and/or grant them permission to collect information about you, then their use of your information is
        governed by their private policy.  Other Corporate Entities: We share much of our data, including personally identifiable
        information about you, with our parent and/or subsidiaries that are committed to serving your online needs and related
        services, throughout the world. Such data will be shared for the sole purpose of enhancing your browsing experience.
        To the extent that these entities have access to your information, they will treat it at least as protective as they treat
        information they obtain from their other members. It is possible that We and/or its subsidiaries, or any combination of
        such, could merge with or be acquired by another business entity. Should such a combination occur, you should expect that
        we would share some or all of your information in order to continue to provide the service. You will receive notice of such
        event (to the extent it occurs).  Law and Order: We cooperate with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties
        to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any
        information about you to law enforcement and other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or
        appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is
        illegal or may expose us or you to legal liability.  ACCESSING, REVIEWING AND CHANGING YOUR PROFILE Following registration,
        you can review and change the information you submitted during registration. You can change your registration information
        such as: name, phone number, and profile. To remove your profile so that others cannot view it, contact our customer support
        team at rsonsdevelopers@gmail.com.  We will retain in our files information you have requested to remove for certain
        circumstances, such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our terms and conditions. Further, such prior
        information is never completely removed from our databases due to technical and legal constraints, including stored \'back up\'
        systems. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personally identifiable information will be completely removed from
        our databases in response to your requests. OTHER INFORMATION COLLECTORS Except as otherwise expressly included in this
        Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that
        you disclose your information to other parties, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you
        disclose to them. To the extent that we use third party advertisers, they adhere to their own privacy policies. Since we do
        not control the privacy policies of the third parties, you are subject to ask questions before you disclose your personal
        information to others.  SECURITY We treat data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access.
        We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by members inside and outside
        the company. We do not recommend transfer of sensitive information details via Application. We follow generally accepted
        industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.
        However, \"perfect security\" does not exist on the Internet. You therefore agree that any security breaches beyond the
        control of our standard security procedures are at your sole risk and discretion.  DISCLAIMER We cannot ensure that all
        of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in
        this Privacy Policy. Therefore, although we are committed to protecting your privacy, we do not promise, and you should
        not expect, that your personal information will always remain private. As a user of the Application, you understand and
        agree that you assume all responsibility and risk for your use of the Application, the internet generally, and the documents
        you post or access and for your conduct on and off the Application.></string>

    <!--_______________________________Tanslate From Here______________________________-->


    <string name="auth_failed">ऑथेंटिकेशन विफल</string>
    <string name="start_phone_auth">लॉग इन करें</string>
    <string name="verify_phone_auth">सत्यापित करें</string>
    <string name="resend_phone_auth">ओटीपी पुनः भेजें</string>
    <string name="hint_phone_number">फ़ोन नंबर</string>
    <string name="hint_verification_code">Verification Code</string>


    <string name="disconnect">डिस्कनेक्ट</string>
    <string name="IMAGE_UPLOADED">चित्र को सफ़लतापूर्वक अपलोड किया गया</string>
    <string name="DATA_SAVED">कहानी सफलतापूर्वक सहेजी गई।</string>
    <string name="UPLOADING_DATA">कृपया प्रतीक्षा करें जब तक हम आपका डेटा सहेज रहे हैं।  </string>
    <string name="UPLOAD_DATA_TITLE">अपलोड हो रहा है ...</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_FILL_ALL">कृपया सभी रिक्त स्थाान भरे।</string>
    <string name="SELECT_DATE">तारीख़ चुनें</string>
    <string name="ENTER_EMAIL_ID">ईमेल</string>
    <string name="SELECT_GENRE">शैली चुनें</string>
    <string name="SELECT_GENDER">लिंग चुनें</string>
    <string name="E_MAIL">ईमेल</string>
    <string name="Enter_name">नाम</string>
    <string name="ENTER_STATUS">अपने बारे में कुछ बतलायें </string>
    <string name="ENTER_TITLE_OF_STORY">कहानी का शीर्षक</string>
    <string name="TAP_TO_ADD_COVER">कहानी का कवर जोड़ने के लिए टैप करें</string>
    <string name="START_WRITING">लेखन प्रारंभ करना ....</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_GIVE_PERMISSIONS">छवि अपलोड करने की अनुमति की आवश्यकता है</string>
    <string name="PUBLISH_STORY">कहानी प्रकाशित करें</string>
    <string name="SAVE_AS_DRAFT">ड्राफ्ट में सहेजें</string>
    <string name="DELETE_STORY">कहानी हटाएं</string>
    <string name="NEW_STORY">नई कहानी</string>
    <string name="SAVING_DATA">डेटा सहेजा जा रहा है </string>
    <string name="PLEASE_WAIT_TEXT">कृपया प्रतीक्षा करें, आपकी कहानी सहेजी जा रही है। </string>
    <string name="PLEASE_ADD_COVER_IMAGE">कहानी को ड्राफ्ट में सहेजने के लिए कवर चित्र जोड़ें </string>
    <string name="IMAGE_UPLOADED_SUCCESSFULLY">चित्र सफलतापूर्वक अपलोड किया गया</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_TRY_AGAIN">कुछ गलत हो गया। कृपया पुन: प्रयास करें।</string>
    <string name="DELETE_SUCCESSFULL">कहानी सफलतापूर्वक हटाई गई</string>
    <string name="EDIT_DRAFT_STORY">ड्राफ्ट की कहानी में बदलाव करें </string>
    <string name="EDIT_PUBLISHED_STORY">प्रकाशित कहानियों में बदलाव करें</string>
    <string name="CREATE_STORY">नई कहानी लिखें </string>
    <string name="search_hint">खोजें ...</string>
    <string name="SEARCH">खोज सेटिंग</string>
    <string name="app_label">app lable</string>
    <string name="SELECT_LANGUAGE">भाषा</string>
    <string name="STORY_KEYWORDS">टैग जोड़ें </string>
    <string name="SOME_MORE_DETAIL">कुछ अतिरिक्त जानकारी</string>
    <string name="PUBLISH">प्रकाशित</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_SELECT_GENER">कृपया शैली चुनें</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_SELECT_LANGUAGE">कृपया भाषा चुनें</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_WAIT_WILE_WE_PUBLISH_STORY">कृपया अपनी कहानी प्रकाशित होने तक प्रतीक्षा करें ......</string>
    <string name="PUBLISHING_STORY">कहानी प्रकाशित हो रही है </string>
    <string name="PLEASE_WAIT">कृपया प्रतीक्षा करें...</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_SELECT_language_and_genre">कृपया भाषा और शैली का चयन करें</string>
    <string name="READ">पढ़ें</string>
    <string name="remove_from_connection">कनेक्शन से हटाएँ </string>
    <string name="add_into_connection">कनेक्शन में जोड़ें </string>
    <string name="ADD_COMMENT">टिप्पणी लिखें</string>
    <string name="SUBMIT">रक्षित करें</string>
    <string name="EDIT">बदलाव करें </string>
    <string name="DELETE">हटाएँ </string>
    <string name="decline_friend_request">कनेक्शन से हटाएँ</string>
    <string name="send_friend_request">जुडिये</string>
    <string name="WRITING">लेखन</string>
    <string name="SEND_MESSAGE">संदेश भेजें</string>
    <string name="WRITE_MESSAGES">संदेश लिखें</string>
    <string name="TRENDING_STORY">बहुचर्चित कहानी</string>
    <string name="SOMETHING_WENT_WRONG">कुछ गलत हो गया। कृपया पुन: प्रयास करें।</string>
    <string name="STORY">कहानियाँ</string>
    <string name="CHAT">बातचीत</string>
    <string name="FOLLOWERS">फ़ॉलोअर्स</string>
    <string name="HOLD_TO_SEND_AUDIO_MESSAGE">Hold to send audio message.</string>
    <string name="DRAFT">ड्राफ्ट</string>
    <string name="ABOUT_STORY">अपने पाठकों को कहानी के विषय में 30 - 50 शब्दों में बताएं। </string>
    <string name="ADD_NEW_CHAPTER">अगला अध्याय जोड़ें </string>
    <string name="CONNECT">जुडिये</string>
    <string name="MESSAGES">संदेश</string>
    <string name="Accept">स्वीकारें</string>
    <string name="Reject">अस्वीकार</string>
    <string name="NEW_CONNECTION_REQUEST">नई कनेक्शन अनुरोध आई है </string>
    <string name="NEW_REQUEST">नया अनुरोध </string>
    <string name="CANCEL_REQUEST">अनुरोध अस्विकार करें </string>
    <string name="IN_your_Connection">जुड़े हैं</string>
    <string name="PROFILE_UPDATED">प्रोफ़ाइल अपडेट</string>
    <string name="PEOPLES">लोग</string>
    <string name="VIEW">देखें</string>


    <string name="Language">भाषा</string>
    <string name="Share">साझा करें</string>
    <string name="Rate_Us">कनेक्टिंग थॉट्स आपको कैसा लग रहा है</string>

    <string name="hindi">हिन्दी</string>
    <string name="english">English</string>
    <string name="bengali">বাংলা</string>
    <string name="gujarati">ગુજરાતી</string>
    <string name="kannada">ಕನ್ನಡ</string>
    <string name="malayalam">മലയാളം</string>
    <string name="marathi">मराठी</string>
    <string name="oriya">ନୀୟ</string>
    <string name="punjabi">ਪੰਜਾਬੀ</string>
    <string name="sanskrit">संस्कृत</string>
    <string name="tamil">தமிழ்</string>
    <string name="telugu">తెలుగు</string>


    <string name="SEARCH_RESULT_FOR">खोज के नतीजे </string>
    <string name="CREATE_AUDIO_STORY">नई ऑडियो कहानी जोड़ें</string>
    <string name="SHARE">साझा करे</string>
    <string name="COMMENT_DELETED">टिप्पणी सफलतापूर्वक हटाई गई</string>
    <string name="ADD_TO_LIBRARY">अपने संग्रह में जोड़ें </string>
    <string name="THIS_cREATIONaLREADYaDDED">यह रचना पहले से ही आपके संग्रह में जोड़ी जा चुकी है। </string>
    <string name="SUCCESS_FULLY_ADDED_TO_LIBRARY">सफलतापूर्वक संग्रह में जोड़ी गई</string>
    <string name="Library">मेरा संग्रह</string>
    <string name="ALREADY_ADDED">संग्रह में जुड़ा है </string>
    <string name="YOUR_COLLECTION">मेरा संग्रह</string>



    <!--__________________________Ad Units Ids________________________________-->

    <!--<string name="admob_app_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544~3347511713</string>
    <string name="ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/8135179316</string>-->


    <string name="admob_CT_app_id">ca-app-pub-6416702975493032~8025337369</string>
    <string name="banner_feed_screen_ad_unit_id_121">ca-app-pub-6416702975493032/5508016473</string>
    <string name="feed_banner_ad_second">ca-app-pub-6416702975493032/7501068079</string>
    <string name="feed_banner_ad_third">ca-app-pub-6416702975493032/8949881113</string>
    <string name="story_read_banner_ad">ca-app-pub-6416702975493032/7664719609</string>
    <string name="story_read_banner_ad_1">ca-app-pub-6416702975493032/6104225929</string>
    <string name="story_chat_banner_ad">ca-app-pub-6416702975493032/5337939162</string>
    <string name="story_first_pageInterstial_ad">ca-app-pub-6416702975493032/1454534477</string>
    <string name="story_read_interstial_ad">ca-app-pub-6416702975493032/4243036268</string>






    <string name="MOVING_ALONE">आप अभी इस समुदाय में किसी से नहीं जुड़े हैं। </string>
    <string name="NO_RESULT_FOUND">कोई परिणाम नहीं मिला</string>
    <string name="NO_INTERNET_CONNECTION">कोई इंटरनेट कनेक्शन नहीं</string>
    <string name="YOU_COLLECTION_IS_EMPTY">आपका संग्रह खाली है</string>
    <string name="History">इतिहास</string>
    <string name="Read_History">इतिहास देखें</string>
    <string name="HISTORY_CLEARED_COMPLETLY">इतिहास ने सफलतापूर्वक साफ़ हो गया</string>
    <string name="Setting">सेटिंग</string>
    <string name="PARTERS">भागीदार बनें</string>
    <string name="HELP">सहायता</string>
    <string name="NEW_CONNECTION_R">नया कनेक्शन अनुरोध</string>
    <string name="LIBRARY_CLEARED">आपका संग्रह सफलतापूर्वक साफ किया गया।</string>
    <string name="NEW_CONNECTION_reQ">कनेक्शन अनुरोध</string>
    <string name="notification">नोटिफिकेशन </string>
    <string name="REPORT">स्टोरी रिपोर्ट</string>
    <string name="YOU_MAY_LIKE">आप इन्हें भी पसंद कर सकते हैं। </string>

    <!--**************************Categories in connecting thoughts******************************-->

    <string name="NEW_STORY_on_ct">नई प्रकाशित हुई कहानियाँ</string>
    <string name="TRENDING_STORY_on_ct">बहुचर्चित कहानियाँ</string>
    <string name="ALL_TIME_BEST_STORY_ON_CT">सर्वश्रेष्ठ कहानियाँ</string>
    <string name="STORY_ON_MOTIVATION">प्रेरणात्मक कहानियाँ</string>
    <string name="STORY_ON_STRUGGLE">संघर्ष को दर्शाती कहानियाँ </string>
    <string name="STORY_ON_DREAM">लोगों के स्वप्न</string>
    <string name="FOLKS_OPINION">विभिन्न विषयों पर लोगों की राय</string>
    <string name="POETRY">कविता संग्रह</string>
    <string name="PATRIOTISM">देशभक्तिपूर्ण विचार</string>
    <string name="STORY_ON_folks_DAY">लोगों के दिन की कहानी </string>
    <string name="STORY_ON_COMEDY">हास्य कहानियाँ </string>
    <string name="STORY_ON_Love">प्यार भरी कहानियाँ</string>
    <string name="STORY_ON_CONFESSION">नया कन्फेशन</string>
    <string name="STORY_ON_MEMORIES">यादों की गहराइयों से कुछ मोती </string>
    <string name="STORY_ON_Remarkabele_Creation">उल्लेखनीय रचनाओं का संग्रह</string>



    <string name="YOUR_STORY_DELETED_SUCCESSFULLY">यह कहानी सफलतापूर्वक हटाई गई</string>
    <string name="NOW_YOUR_STORY_MOVE_TO_DRAFT_SECTION">आपकी कहानी को ड्राफ्ट में सहेजा गया है।</string>
    <string name="DO_YOU_REALLY_WANT_TO_EDIT">क्या आप यकीनन बदलाव करना चाहते हैं?</string>
    <string name="EDITING_PUBLISH_STORY_MESSAGE">प्रकाशित कहानी में बदलाव करने पर उसे कनेक्टिंग थॉट्स से अप्रकाशित कर दिया जावेगा,
        और ड्राफ्ट में सहेजा जावेगा। आप अपनी कहानी को ड्राफ्ट खंड से पुनः प्रकाशित कर कनेक्टिंग थॉट्स के उपयोगकर्तों के लिए उपलब्ध करा सकते हैं।
</string>
    <string name="CANCEL">रद्द करें</string>
    <string name="DO_YOU_REALLY_WANT_TO_DELETE">क्या आप अपने फैसले पर निश्चित हैं ?</string>
    <string name="DELETING_STORY_MESSAGE">इस कहानी को हटाने के बाद आप इसे फिर से पुनर्प्राप्त नहीं कर सकते। इसे स्थायी रूप से हटा दिया जाएगा
         क्या आप वाकई आगे बढ़ना चाहते हैं?</string>
    <string name="WHAT_INAPPROPRIATE_CONTENT">आपको किस प्रकार की अनुपयुक्त सामग्री मिली है?</string>
    <string name="INAPPROPRIATE_CONTENT_HINT">आप इस कहानी के लिए रिपोर्ट कर सकतें हैं यदि ये किसी भी प्रकार की नफरत या उत्पीड़न को बढ़ावा देती है,
        या इस कहानी में अश्लील और अभद्र भाषा का प्रयोग किया गया है, या फिर यह कहानी आपकी अनुमति के बिना आपकी व्यक्तिगत जानकारी को साझा कर रही है। </string>

    <string name="SAVE_THE_CHANGES">परिवर्तनों को सुरक्षित करें !</string>
    <string name="DO_YOU_WANT_TO_SAVE_CHANGES_IN_STORY">क्या आप अपनी कहानी में परिवर्तनों को सहेजना चाहते हैं?</string>
    <string name="NO">नहीं</string>
    <string name="YES">हाँ</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_WRITE_SOME_THING_BEFORE_PUBLISH">कहानी प्रकाशित करने से पहले कृपया कुछ लिखें।</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_GIVE_TITLE_TO_YOUR_STORY">कृपया अपनी कहानी का शीर्षक लिखें। </string>
    <string name="UPDATED_ON">संशोधित किया गया :</string>
    <string name="PUBLISHED_ON">प्रकाशित किया गया :</string>
    <string name="CHANGE_COVER_IMAGE">कवर छवि बदलें</string>
    <string name="REMOVE_COVER_IMAGE">कवर छवि हटाएँ </string>
    <string name="STORY_COVER_DELETED_SUCCESSFULLY">कहानी कवर सफलतापूर्वक हटा दिया गया</string>
    <string name="WAIT_FOR_MOMENT">कुछ पल को रुकें </string>
    <string name="NO_UPDATE_TO_SAVE">कहानी में कोई बदलाव नहीं किया गया है, जिसे सहेजने की आवश्यकता है। </string>
    <string name="NOTHING_TO_SHOW">इस भाषा में कोई भी सामग्री उपलब्ध नहीं है।</string>
    <string name="YOU_HAVE_NOT_PUBLISHED_STORY_YET">आपने अभी तक कोई भी कहानी प्रकाशित नहीं की है।</string>
    <string name="UPLOADING_IMAGE">छवि अपलोड हो रही है </string>
    <string name="PLEASE_WAIT_FOR_IMAGE">कृपया प्रतीक्षा करें जब तक हम छवि को संसाधित और सहेज रहे हैं। </string>
    <string name="NO_STORY_IN_YOUR_DRAFT_SECTION">आपके ड्राफ्ट खंड में कोई उपलब्ध कहानी नहीं है। </string>
    <string name="COPYRIGHT_ISSUE">कॉपीराइट समस्या</string>
    <string name="GARBAGE_CONTANT">बेकार सामग्री जो कनेक्टिंग थॉट्स से संबंध नहीं रखती </string>
    <string name="INAPPROPRIATE_CONTENT">अनुचित सामग्री</string>
    <string name="REPORT_EMAIL">ईमेल *</string>
    <string name="REPORT_NAME">नाम *</string>
    <string name="YOU_CAN_ENTER_YOUR_PROBLEM_HERE">अपनी समस्या यहां लिखें ...</string>
    <string name="REPORT_TO_STORY">कहानी को रिपोर्ट करें</string>
    <string name="CHOOSE_LANGUAGE">भाषा चुनें</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_CHOOSE_LANGUGE">कृपया आगे बढ़ने के लिए भाषा चुनें</string>
    <string name="SAVE">रक्षित करें </string>
    <string name="CHOOSE_YOUR_DESIRED_LANGUAGE">अपनी भाषा का चयन करें</string>
    <string name="ENTER_VELID_NUMBER">कृपया वैध मोबाइल नंबर दर्ज करें</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_ACCEPT_TERMS_AND_CONDITIOIN">कृपया नियम और शर्तें स्वीकार करें</string>
    <string name="PHONE_NUMBER">फोन नंबर</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_BE_PATIENT">कृपया धैर्य रखें, डेटा लोड हो रहा है।</string>
    <string name="PHONE_NUMBER_REPORT">फोन नंबर *</string>
    <string name="OK">Ok</string>
    <string name="YOU_CAN_REPORT_FOR">आप रिपोर्ट कर सकते हैं</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_PROVIDE_YOUR_NAME">कृपया नाम लिखें</string>
    <string name="PROVIDE_YOUR_NUMBER">कृपया फोन नंबर प्रदान करें</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_PROVIDE_EMAIL">कृपया ईमेल आईडी प्रदान करें</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_WRITE_ABOUT_YOUR_PROBLEM">कृपया अपनी समस्या का उल्लेख करें</string>
    <string name="WE_WILL_TAKE_ACTION">आपकी रिपोर्ट की जांच के बाद हम उचित कार्रवाई करेंगे</string>
    <string name="Incomming_report">आने वाली रिपोर्ट</string>
    <string name="REPORT_TYPE">रिपोर्ट का प्रकार</string>
    <string name="REPORTER_LIST">रिपोर्ट सूची</string>
    <string name="OPEN_STORY">कहानी पढ़ें</string>
    <string name="TAKE_ACTION">कार्रवाई करें</string>
    <string name="REPORTED_BY">रिपोर्ट की गई </string>
    <string name="SUSPEND_STORY">अप्रकाशित कहानी</string>
    <string name="IGRORE_REPORT">रिपोर्ट को अनदेखा करें</string>
    <string name="TAKE_ACTION_AGAINST_REPORT">कार्रवाई करें</string>
    <string name="DO_YOU_REALLY_WANT_TO_SUSPAND_STORY">क्या आप यकीनन में कहानी को अप्रकाशित करना चाहते हैं?</string>
    <string name="DO_YOU_REALLY_WANT_TO_REJCT_REPORT">क्या आप वाकई इस रिपोर्ट को नकली घोषित करना चाहते हैं?</string>
    <string name="STORY_UNPUBLISHED_SUCCESSFULLY">कहानी सफलतापूर्वक अप्रकाशित  हो गई </string>
    <string name="SUBMITING_REPORT">रिपोर्ट सबमिट हो रही है </string>
    <string name="PLEASE_WAIT_WHILE_WE_SUBMIT_REPORT">कृपया प्रतीक्षा करें जब तक हम आपकी रिपोर्ट सबमिट कर रहे हैं।</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_WAIT_WHILE_WE_UNPUBLISH_STORY">कृपया प्रतीक्षा करें जब तक कहानी के निलंबन की प्रकिया जारी है </string>
    <string name="PLEASE_WAIT_WHILE_WE_REJECTING_REPORT">कृपया रिपोर्ट को खारिज करने तक प्रतीक्षा करें।</string>
    <string name="REPORT_DECLARED_AS_FAKE">रिपोर्ट को नकली घोषित किया गया</string>
    <string name="NO_REPORT_YET">अभी तक कोई रिपोर्ट नहीं है</string>
    <string name="SHARE_WITH">शेयर करें</string>
    <string name="SELECT_PICTURE">चित्र चुनें</string>
    <string name="VERIFY">सत्यापित करें</string>
    <string name="SEND_otp">ओटीपी भेजें</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_ENTER_YOUR_NAME">कृपया अपना नाम दर्ज करें ताकि लोग आपकी पहचान कर सकें।</string>
    <string name="ENTER_NAME">नाम लिखें</string>
    <string name="SELECT_CHOOSE">भाषा चुनिए</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_ENTER_YOUR_NAME_BEFORE_SAVING_IT">सहेजने से पहले अपना नाम दर्ज करें।</string>
    <string name="FRIENDS">मित्र </string>
    <string name="NOTIFICATION">नोटिफिकेशन </string>
    <string name="SENT_A_CONNECTION_REQUEST">आपसे जुड़ना चाहते हैं </string>
    <string name="CLEAR_NOTIFICATION">नोटिफिकेशन मिटाएं</string>
    <string name="MIRACLE_OFFLINE_MESSAGE">चमत्कार अपने आप नहीं होते, कई लोग दफ़न हो जाते हैं उस एक चमत्कार के लिए जिसे वो चमत्कार कह सकें।
        जिनमे अपने चमत्कार के लिए दफ़न होने की क्षमता होती है वही एक दिन अपने चमत्कार की ओर अग्रसर होते हैं।   \n
                                        -------- कनेक्टिंग थॉट्स टीम द्वारा</string>

    <string name="HIDE_YOUR_IDENTITY">क्या आप इस कहानी में अपनी पहचान छुपाना चाहते हैं ?</string>
    <string name="UNKNOWN">अज्ञात</string>
    <string name="SORRY_AUTHOR_OF_THIS_STORY_IS_UNKNOWN">खेद है इस कहानी का लेखक अज्ञात है।</string>
    <string name="ABOUT_US">हमारे बारे में</string>
    <string name="MY_profile">मेरी प्रोफाइल</string>
    <string name="BIRTH_DAY">जन्म दिवस</string>
    <string name="gender">लिंग</string>
    <string name="CHECK_OUT_CONNECTING_THOUGHTS">Check out connecting thoughts and meet people like you.</string>
    <string name="CLEAR_HISTORY">इतिहास मिटाएं</string>
    <string name="CLEAR_LIBRARY">संग्रह मिटाएं</string>
    <string name="YOU_DID_NOT_READ_ANY_STORY_YET">आपने अभी तक कोई भी कहानी नहीं पढ़ी है।</string>

    <string name="HOW_TO_WRITE_IN_CONNECTING_THOUGHTS">कैसे लिखें और प्रकाशित करें?</string>
    <string name="HOW_TO_SEND_CONNECTION_REQUEST">कनेक्शन अनुरोध कैसे भेजें?</string>
    <string name="HOW_ACCEPT_CONNECTION_REQUEST">कनेक्शन अनुरोध कैसे स्वीकार करें?</string>
    <string name="SEND_YOUR_FIRST_MESSAGE">अपना पहला संदेश कैसे भेजें?</string>
    <string name="START_CONVERSATION">कैसे बातचीत शुरू?</string>
    <string name="ENTER_MOBILE_NO_TO_VERIFY">मोबाइल नंबर दर्ज करें सत्यापित करने के लिए</string>
    <string name="VERIFY_PHONE_NO">फोन नंबर</string>
    <string name="I_ACCEPT">मैं स्वीकारता हूँ </string>
    <string name="terms_and_condition_action_btn">\&#160; नियम एवं शर्तों को *</string>
    <string name="FOR_ANY_KIND_OF_SUGGESTION_OR_PROBLEM">क्या आप कनेक्टिंग थॉट्स के लिए कोई सुझाव देना चाहते हैं ?</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_INSTALL_GMAIL_TO_SEND">Please install gmail into your device</string>
    <string name="I_WANT_TO_SUGGEST_SOMETHING">I want to suggest</string>
    <string name="MY_SUGGESTIONS">My suggestions</string>


    <string name="WHAT_IS_PURPOSE_OF_CT_1">कनेक्टिंग थॉट्स एक ऑनलाइन मंच है जहां लोग अपनी रचना लिख सकते हैं और प्रकाशित कर सकते हैं।</string>
    <string name="WHAT_IS_PURPOSE_OF_CT_2">कनेक्टिंग थॉट्स का मुख्य उद्देश्य लोगों को ऐसा मंच प्रदान करना जहाँ लोग अपनी सफलताओं,
        अपनी उपलब्धियों, अपनी हानि, अपनी यादों और अपने जीवन  के अनुभवों की कहानियों को साझा कर सकें।</string>
    <string name="WHAT_IS_PURPOSE_OF_CT_3">कनेक्टिंग थॉट्स में, लोग समान प्रकार की सोच के लोगों से मिलते हैं।</string>
    <string name="WHAT_IS_PURPOSE_OF_CT_4">यदि आप इस समुदाय को बढ़ने के लिए किसी भी तरह से मदद करना चाहते हैं, तो हमारी टीम में आपका स्वागत है।</string>
    <string name="send_MAIL_TO_US">हमें मेल भेजें</string>
    <string name="WHAT_IS_PURPOSE_OF_CT_5">यदि आप आर्थिक मदद करना चाहते हैं, तो इस बटन पर क्लिक करें।</string>
    <string name="FINIANCIAL_SUPPORT">आर्थिक सहायता</string>
    <string name="I_WANT_TO_JOIN_CT">I want to join connecting thoughts</string>
    <string name="I_WANT_GROW_CT">I want to help this community</string>
    <string name="BECOME_A_PARTNER">Become a partner</string>
    <string name="HOW_MUCH_YOU_WANT_TO_HELP">Enter Amount</string>
    <string name="Proceed">Proceed</string>
    <string name="ENTER_AMOUNT">Enter Donation Amount</string>
    <string name="Donation">Donation</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_ENTER_DONATION_AMOUNT">Please enter donation amount more then zero</string>
    <string name="OR">या गूगल के साथ साइन इन करें</string>
    <string name="UPDATE">अपडेट करें</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_AVILABELE">अपडेट उपलब्ध है</string>
    <string name="NEW_UPDATE_AVILABLE">नमस्कार दोस्तों, हम जानते हैं कि आप जल्दी में हैं लेकिन आपको इस ऐप को अपडेट करने की ज़रूरत है
        ताकि आप इस ऐप का बेहतर अनुभव प्राप्त कर सकें।</string>
    <string name="PRIVECY_POLICY">Privacy policy</string>
    <string name="terms_and_condition_action">Terms &amp; condition</string>

    <string name="READ_SETTING">Read setting</string>
    <string name="SORRY_TEXT_SIZE_NOT_DECREASES">अक्षरों का आकार इससे अधिक नहीं घट सकता।</string>
    <string name="SORRY_TEXT_SIZE_NOT_INCREASES">अक्षरों का आकार इससे अधिक नहीं बढ़ सकता।</string>
    <string name="LOADING_USER_DATA">कृपया प्रतीक्षा करें जब तक डेटा लोड हो रहा है। </string>
    <string name="WRITE_YOUR_MESSAGE">Write your message</string>

    <string name="TERMS_AND_CONDITION">Terms and condition</string>
    <string name="PRIVACY_POLICY">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="ABOUT_US_CONNECTING_THOUGHTS">About Connecting Thoughts</string>
    <string name="ABOUT_CONNECTING_THOUGHTS">We are heighly dedicated team</string>



    <string name="LOAD_MORE_COMMENT">सभी टिप्पणियाँ लोड करें</string>
    <string name="CONNECTING_THOUGHTS_PROMO">कनेक्टिंग थॉट्स प्रोमो</string>
    <string name="GO_TO_HELP">मदद में जाएँ </string>
    <string name="DO_YOU_WANT_SOME_HELP">क्या आपको कुछ मदद चाहिए ?</string>
    <string name="GO_TO_HELP_MESSAGE">यदि आपको कनेक्टिंग थॉट्स इस्तेमाल करने में किसी भी प्रकार की परेशानी हो रही है,
        तो आप कनेक्टिंग थॉट्स के मदद खंड में जा कर सहायता ले सकते हैं।</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_GIVE_PERMISSIONS_FOR_IMAGE_MESSAGE">मल्टीमीडिया फ़ाइलों तक पहुंचने की अनुमति की आवश्यकता है।</string>
    <string name="ONLY_IMAGE_FILE_IS_SUPPORTED">क्षमा कीजिए! केवल छायाचित्र प्रकार की फाइलें चुन सकते हैं। </string>
    <string name="OPEN_AUTHOR_DETAIL">कहानी के लेखक विवरण</string>
    <string name="AUTHOR_DETAIL">लेखक विवरण </string>
    <string name="NO_NEW_CONNECTION_REQUEST">कोई भी नया कनेक्शन अनुरोध नहीं </string>
    <string name="YOU_HAVE_NOT_STARTED_ANY_CONVERSATION_YET">अपने अभी तक किसी से भी बातचीत करना शुरू नहीं किया है।</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_RATE_FIRST">कृपया पहले रेट करें </string>
</resources>
