<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Connecting Thoughts</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="SIGN_UP_TEXT">New to Connecting Thoughts ? Sign Up</string>


    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password (optional)</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>


    <string name="PRIVACY_POLICY_TEXT">Connecting thoughts team is the creator of this Privacy Policy operate at connecting thoughts
        (the ‘Application’) ensure our commitment to your privacy vis-à-vis the protection of your priceless information.
        In order to endow you with our uninterrupted use of services, we may collect and, in some circumstances,
        disclose information about you. To enhance better protection of your privacy we provide this notice explaining
        our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.
        If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, you should contact our Customer Support Desk at
        rsonsdevelopers@gmail.com.  OVERVIEW We commit to respecting your online privacy data. We further recognize your need
        for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information (\"Personal Information\")
        you share with us. Information that is considered personal about you by us includes, but is not limited to, your name,
        address, email address or other contact information.  Our application offers multiple services which can be accessed by
        registering with us by providing the following information.  Mobile number; User operated 4-digit passkey; Name; E-mail Address.
        NOTIFICATION OF MODIFICATIONS AND CHANGES TO THE T&amp;C AND PRIVACY POLICY We reserve the right to change the Terms and
        Privacy Policy from time to time as seen fit, without any intimation to you, and your continued use of the application
        will signify your acceptance of any amendment to these terms.  You are therefore advised to re-read the Terms of Service
        and this Privacy Policy on a regular basis. Should it be that you do not accept any of the modifications or amendments
        to the Terms, you may terminate your use of this application immediately.  INFORMATION WE COLLECT Our application’s
        online requisition form requires users to give us contact information (like your name, telephone number and email address).
        As a connecting thoughts member you are required to provide a valid email address at registration and choose a username
        or alias that represents your identity on our application.  In furtherance to this we also collect device specific
        information such as your International Mobile Equipment Identifiers (IMEI) without your intervention.  Certain information,
        such as your name, e-mail addresses, is collected in order to, among other things, verify your identity and for use as
        account numbers in our record system. Email addresses, Geo-locations, Intellectual Property, listings viewed, any
        information entered in the contact us form or any other form displayed on any section of the application are also collected.
        OUR USE OF YOUR INFORMATION Your contact information is also used to contact you when necessary. We use your IP address to
        help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Application. Your IP address is also used to help identify
        you and to gather broad demographic information. Finally, we may use your IP address to help protect our partners and
        ourselves from fraud. We will continue to enhance our security procedures as new technology becomes available.
        We will transfer information about you if we are acquired by or merged with another company. In this event,
        we will notify you by email or by putting a prominent notice on the application before information about you is transferred
        and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.  We may release your personal information to a third-party in order
        comply with a Court Order or other similar legal procedure, or when we believe in good faith that such disclosure is
        necessary to comply with the law; prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss; or investigate or take action
        regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, or violations of Our Terms of Use. We may disclose personally identifiable
        information to parties in compliance with our Copyright Policy as mentioned in the Terms of Use as we in our sole discretion
        believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy,
        or other unlawful activity. In such events, we may disclose name, address, country, phone number, email address and company
        name.  CONFIDENTIALITY You further acknowledge that the Application may contain information which is designated confidential
        by us and that you shall not disclose such information without our prior written consent.  Your information is regarded as
        confidential and therefore will not be divulged to any third party, unless if legally required to do so to the appropriate
        authorities.  We will not sell, share, or rent your personal information to any third party or use your email address for
        unsolicited mail. Any emails sent by us will only be in connection with the provision of agreed services and products.
        OUR DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private
        communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in
        this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting and foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to
        the government, law enforcement agencies or third parties. Under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully
        intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or members may abuse or misuse your information that they
        collect from our Application. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not
        promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications would always
        remain private.  As a matter of policy, we do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any
        third party. However, the following describes some of the ways that your personally identifiable information may be disclosed.
        External Service Providers: There may be a number of services offered by external service providers that help you use our
        Application. If you choose to use these optional services, and in the course of doing so, disclose information to the external
        service providers, and/or grant them permission to collect information about you, then their use of your information is
        governed by their private policy.  Other Corporate Entities: We share much of our data, including personally identifiable
        information about you, with our parent and/or subsidiaries that are committed to serving your online needs and related
        services, throughout the world. Such data will be shared for the sole purpose of enhancing your browsing experience.
        To the extent that these entities have access to your information, they will treat it at least as protective as they treat
        information they obtain from their other members. It is possible that We and/or its subsidiaries, or any combination of
        such, could merge with or be acquired by another business entity. Should such a combination occur, you should expect that
        we would share some or all of your information in order to continue to provide the service. You will receive notice of such
        event (to the extent it occurs).  Law and Order: We cooperate with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties
        to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any
        information about you to law enforcement and other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or
        appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is
        illegal or may expose us or you to legal liability.  ACCESSING, REVIEWING AND CHANGING YOUR PROFILE Following registration,
        you can review and change the information you submitted during registration. You can change your registration information
        such as: name, phone number, and profile. To remove your profile so that others cannot view it, contact our customer support
        team at rsonsdevelopers@gmail.com.  We will retain in our files information you have requested to remove for certain
        circumstances, such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our terms and conditions. Further, such prior
        information is never completely removed from our databases due to technical and legal constraints, including stored \'back up\'
        systems. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personally identifiable information will be completely removed from
        our databases in response to your requests. OTHER INFORMATION COLLECTORS Except as otherwise expressly included in this
        Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that
        you disclose your information to other parties, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you
        disclose to them. To the extent that we use third party advertisers, they adhere to their own privacy policies. Since we do
        not control the privacy policies of the third parties, you are subject to ask questions before you disclose your personal
        information to others.  SECURITY We treat data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access.
        We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by members inside and outside
        the company. We do not recommend transfer of sensitive information details via Application. We follow generally accepted
        industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.
        However, \"perfect security\" does not exist on the Internet. You therefore agree that any security breaches beyond the
        control of our standard security procedures are at your sole risk and discretion.  DISCLAIMER We cannot ensure that all
        of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in
        this Privacy Policy. Therefore, although we are committed to protecting your privacy, we do not promise, and you should
        not expect, that your personal information will always remain private. As a user of the Application, you understand and
        agree that you assume all responsibility and risk for your use of the Application, the internet generally, and the documents
        you post or access and for your conduct on and off the Application.></string>

    <string name="label_phone_auth">Phone Number Authentication</string>
    <string name="desc_phone_auth">Use a phone number to authenticate with Firebase.</string>

    <string name="label_anonymous_auth">Anonymous Authentication</string>
    <string name="desc_anonymous_auth">Sign in anonymously and then later upgrade to a full Firebase Auth user.</string>

    <string name="label_custom_auth">Custom Authentication</string>
    <string name="desc_custom_auth">Use a custom token signed by your own server to authenticate with Firebase.</string>

    <string name="label_firebase_ui">FirebaseUI Auth</string>
    <string name="desc_firebase_ui">Use the FirebaseUI-Android library to authenticate with Firebase.</string>


    <string name="hint_user_id">User ID</string>
    <string name="get_custom_token">Get Token</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="create_account">Create Account</string>
    <string name="sign_out">Sign Out</string>
    <string name="verify_email">Verify Email</string>
    <string name="disconnect">Disconnect</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading…</string>
    <string name="custom_token">Custom Token</string>
    <string name="signed_in">Logged in !</string>
    <string name="signed_out">You are not logged in !</string>
    <string name="token_null">Token: null</string>
    <string name="hint_email">Email</string>
    <string name="hint_password">Password</string>
    <string name="desc_firebase_lockup">Firebase logo and name</string>

    <string name="status_code_sent">Code Sent</string>
    <string name="status_verification_failed">Verification failed</string>
    <string name="status_verification_succeeded">Verification succeeded</string>
    <string name="status_sign_in_failed">Sign-in failed</string>
    <string name="instant_validation">(instant validation)</string>

    <string name="firebase_status_fmt">Firebase User: %s</string>
    <string name="firebase_user_management">Firebase User Management</string>

    <string name="google_status_fmt">Google User: %s</string>
    <string name="google_title_text">Google Sign In</string>

    <string name="facebook_status_fmt">Facebook User: %s</string>
    <string name="facebook_title_text">Facebook Login</string>

    <string name="emailpassword_status_fmt">Email User: %1$s (verified: %2$b)</string>
    <string name="emailpassword_title_text">Email and Password</string>

    <string name="phone_title_text">Phone Number</string>

    <string name="twitter_status_fmt">Twitter User: %s</string>
    <string name="twitter_title_text">Twitter Login</string>

    <string name="firebaseui_status_fmt">Firebase User: %s</string>
    <string name="firebaseui_title_text">FirebaseUI Auth</string>

    <string name="id_fmt">User ID: %s</string>
    <string name="email_fmt">Email: %s</string>



    <!--_______________________________Tanslate From Here______________________________-->



    <string name="auth_failed">Authentication failed</string>
    <string name="start_phone_auth">Login</string>
    <string name="verify_phone_auth">Verify</string>
    <string name="resend_phone_auth">Resend OTP</string>
    <string name="hint_phone_number">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="hint_verification_code">Verification Code</string>

    <string name="IMAGE_UPLOADED">Successfully uploaded the image.</string>
    <string name="DATA_SAVED">Story Saved Successfully.</string>
    <string name="UPLOADING_DATA">Please wait while we saving your data.</string>
    <string name="UPLOAD_DATA_TITLE">Uploading...</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_FILL_ALL">Please fill all fields.</string>
    <string name="SELECT_DATE">Select Date</string>
    <string name="ENTER_EMAIL_ID">Email</string>
    <string name="SELECT_GENRE">Choose Genre</string>
    <string name="SELECT_GENDER">Select Gender</string>
    <string name="E_MAIL">Email</string>
    <string name="Enter_name">Name</string>
    <string name="ENTER_STATUS">Describe Yourself</string>
    <string name="ENTER_TITLE_OF_STORY">Title of story</string>
    <string name="TAP_TO_ADD_COVER">Tap to add cover</string>
    <string name="START_WRITING">Start Writing ....</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_GIVE_PERMISSIONS">Need a permission to upload image.</string>
    <string name="PUBLISH_STORY">Publish Story</string>
    <string name="SAVE_AS_DRAFT">Save as draft</string>
    <string name="DELETE_STORY">Delete story</string>
    <string name="NEW_STORY">New Story</string>
    <string name="SAVING_DATA">Saving Data</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_WAIT_TEXT">Please wait while we saving your story.</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_ADD_COVER_IMAGE">Please add cover image to save story in draft.</string>
    <string name="IMAGE_UPLOADED_SUCCESSFULLY">Image Uploaded Successfully.</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_TRY_AGAIN">Something went wrong please try again.</string>
    <string name="DELETE_SUCCESSFULL">Story deleted successfully</string>
    <string name="EDIT_DRAFT_STORY">Edit Draft Story</string>
    <string name="EDIT_PUBLISHED_STORY">Edit Published Story</string>
    <string name="CREATE_STORY">Add New Story</string>
    <string name="search_hint">Search...</string>
    <string name="SEARCH">Search setting</string>
    <string name="app_label">app lable</string>
    <string name="SELECT_LANGUAGE">Language</string>
    <string name="STORY_KEYWORDS">Add Tag</string>
    <string name="SOME_MORE_DETAIL">Some Extra Detail</string>
    <string name="PUBLISH">PUBLISH</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_SELECT_GENER">Please Select Genre</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_SELECT_LANGUAGE">Please Select Language</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_WAIT_WILE_WE_PUBLISH_STORY">Please wait while we publishing your story......</string>
    <string name="PUBLISHING_STORY">Publishing Story</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_WAIT">Please wait...</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_SELECT_language_and_genre">Please select language and genre.</string>
    <string name="READ">Read</string>
    <string name="remove_from_connection">Remove From Connection</string>
    <string name="add_into_connection">Add To Your Connection</string>
    <string name="ADD_COMMENT">Add Comment</string>
    <string name="SUBMIT">Submit</string>
    <string name="EDIT">Edit</string>
    <string name="DELETE">Delete</string>
    <string name="decline_friend_request">Remove From Connection</string>
    <string name="send_friend_request">Connect</string>
    <string name="WRITING">Writing</string>
    <string name="SEND_MESSAGE">Send Message</string>
    <string name="WRITE_MESSAGES">Write message</string>
    <string name="TRENDING_STORY">Trending Story</string>
    <string name="SOMETHING_WENT_WRONG">Please try again something went wrong.</string>
    <string name="STORY">STORY</string>
    <string name="CHAT">CHAT</string>
    <string name="FOLLOWERS">FOLLOWERS</string>
    <string name="HOLD_TO_SEND_AUDIO_MESSAGE">Hold to send audio message.</string>
    <string name="DRAFT">Draft</string>
    <string name="ABOUT_STORY">Tell your readers about story in 30 - 50 words.</string>
    <string name="ADD_NEW_CHAPTER">Add Another Chapter</string>
    <string name="CONNECT">Connect</string>
    <string name="MESSAGES">Message</string>
    <string name="Accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="Reject">Reject</string>
    <string name="NEW_CONNECTION_REQUEST">New Connection Request From</string>
    <string name="NEW_REQUEST">New Request</string>
    <string name="CANCEL_REQUEST">Cancel Request</string>
    <string name="IN_your_Connection">Connected</string>
    <string name="PROFILE_UPDATED">Profile Updated</string>
    <string name="PEOPLES">Peoples</string>
    <string name="VIEW">View</string>




    <string name="Language">Language</string>
    <string name="Share">Share</string>
    <string name="Rate_Us">Rate Us</string>

    <string name="hindi">हिन्दी</string>
    <string name="english">English</string>
    <string name="bengali">বাংলা</string>
    <string name="gujarati">ગુજરાતી</string>
    <string name="kannada">ಕನ್ನಡ</string>
    <string name="malayalam">മലയാളം</string>
    <string name="marathi">मराठी</string>
    <string name="oriya">ନୀୟ</string>
    <string name="punjabi">ਪੰਜਾਬੀ</string>
    <string name="sanskrit">संस्कृत</string>
    <string name="tamil">தமிழ்</string>
    <string name="telugu">తెలుగు</string>


    <string name="SEARCH_RESULT_FOR">Search result for</string>
    <string name="CREATE_AUDIO_STORY">Add new audio Story</string>
    <string name="SHARE">Share</string>
    <string name="COMMENT_DELETED">Comment Deleted Successfully</string>
    <string name="ADD_TO_LIBRARY">Add To Library</string>
    <string name="THIS_cREATIONaLREADYaDDED">This creation has already added into library.</string>
    <string name="SUCCESS_FULLY_ADDED_TO_LIBRARY">Successfully added to library.</string>
    <string name="Library">Library</string>
    <string name="ALREADY_ADDED">Added to Library</string>
    <string name="YOUR_COLLECTION">Library Collection</string>



    <!--__________________________Ad Units Ids________________________________-->

        <!--<string name="admob_app_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544~3347511713</string>
        <string name="ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/8135179316</string>-->

    <string name="admob_CT_app_id">ca-app-pub-6416702975493032~8025337369</string>
    <string name="banner_feed_screen_ad_unit_id_121">ca-app-pub-6416702975493032/5508016473</string>
    <string name="feed_banner_ad_second">ca-app-pub-6416702975493032/7501068079</string>
    <string name="feed_banner_ad_third">ca-app-pub-6416702975493032/8949881113</string>
    <string name="story_read_banner_ad">ca-app-pub-6416702975493032/7664719609</string>
    <string name="story_read_banner_ad_1">ca-app-pub-6416702975493032/6104225929</string>
    <string name="story_chat_banner_ad">ca-app-pub-6416702975493032/5337939162</string>
    <string name="story_first_pageInterstial_ad">ca-app-pub-6416702975493032/1454534477</string>
    <string name="story_read_interstial_ad">ca-app-pub-6416702975493032/4243036268</string>



    <string name="MOVING_ALONE">Currently your are alone in the forest.</string>
    <string name="NO_RESULT_FOUND">No result found</string>
    <string name="NO_INTERNET_CONNECTION">No internet connection</string>
    <string name="YOU_COLLECTION_IS_EMPTY">Your collection is empty.</string>
    <string name="History">History</string>
    <string name="Read_History">Read History</string>
    <string name="HISTORY_CLEARED_COMPLETLY">History Cleared Successfully.</string>
    <string name="Setting">Setting</string>
    <string name="PARTERS">Become a Partner</string>
    <string name="HELP">Help</string>
    <string name="NEW_CONNECTION_R">New Connection Request</string>
    <string name="LIBRARY_CLEARED">Library Cleared Successfully</string>
    <string name="NEW_CONNECTION_reQ">Connection Request</string>
    <string name="notification">Notification</string>
    <string name="REPORT">Report</string>
    <string name="YOU_MAY_LIKE">You may like</string>

    <!--**************************Categories in connecting thoughts******************************-->

    <string name="NEW_STORY_on_ct">Recent Stories</string>
    <string name="TRENDING_STORY_on_ct">Trending Stories</string>
    <string name="ALL_TIME_BEST_STORY_ON_CT">All Time Best Stories</string>
    <string name="STORY_ON_MOTIVATION">Stories on Motivation</string>
    <string name="STORY_ON_STRUGGLE">Stories on Struggle</string>
    <string name="STORY_ON_DREAM">Dreams of Peoples</string>
    <string name="FOLKS_OPINION">People\'s Opinion</string>
    <string name="POETRY">New in Poetry</string>
    <string name="PATRIOTISM">Patriotic Thoughts</string>
    <string name="STORY_ON_folks_DAY">Stories About Folks Day</string>
    <string name="STORY_ON_COMEDY">Stories in Comedy</string>
    <string name="STORY_ON_Love">Stories in Love</string>
    <string name="STORY_ON_CONFESSION">New Confession</string>
    <string name="STORY_ON_MEMORIES">New in Memories</string>
    <string name="STORY_ON_Remarkabele_Creation">Stories in Remarkable Creation</string>



    <string name="YOUR_STORY_DELETED_SUCCESSFULLY">This story deleted successfully.</string>
    <string name="NOW_YOUR_STORY_MOVE_TO_DRAFT_SECTION">Now your story move to draft section.</string>
    <string name="DO_YOU_REALLY_WANT_TO_EDIT">Do you really want to edit ?</string>
    <string name="EDITING_PUBLISH_STORY_MESSAGE">While editing your published story it will be unpublished
        from Connecting Thoughts and moved to your draft section. You can publish it again to make available for Connecting Thoughts users.</string>
    <string name="CANCEL">Cancel</string>
    <string name="DO_YOU_REALLY_WANT_TO_DELETE">Are you sure ?</string>
    <string name="DELETING_STORY_MESSAGE">After deletion of this story you can not recover it again. It will be deleted permanently.
        Are you sure want to proceed ?</string>
    <string name="WHAT_INAPPROPRIATE_CONTENT">What kind of inappropriate content you have found ?</string>
    <string name="INAPPROPRIATE_CONTENT_HINT">You can report to this story if it promotes hate or harassment. You can also
    report to this story if it contain pornographic  content or sharing your personal information without your permission.</string>
    <string name="SAVE_THE_CHANGES">Save the changes !</string>
    <string name="DO_YOU_WANT_TO_SAVE_CHANGES_IN_STORY">Do you want to save the changes in your story ?</string>
    <string name="NO">No</string>
    <string name="YES">Yes</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_WRITE_SOME_THING_BEFORE_PUBLISH">Please write something before publish story.</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_GIVE_TITLE_TO_YOUR_STORY">Please give title to your story.</string>
    <string name="UPDATED_ON">Updated on :</string>
    <string name="PUBLISHED_ON">Published on :</string>
    <string name="CHANGE_COVER_IMAGE">Change Cover Image</string>
    <string name="REMOVE_COVER_IMAGE">Remove Cover Image</string>
    <string name="STORY_COVER_DELETED_SUCCESSFULLY">Story cover removed successfully.</string>
    <string name="WAIT_FOR_MOMENT">Wait For Moment</string>
    <string name="NO_UPDATE_TO_SAVE">No changes in story content to save.</string>
    <string name="NOTHING_TO_SHOW">No content available in this language.</string>
    <string name="YOU_HAVE_NOT_PUBLISHED_STORY_YET">You haven\'t published any story yet.</string>
    <string name="UPLOADING_IMAGE">Uploading Image</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_WAIT_FOR_IMAGE">Please wait while we process and saving image.</string>
    <string name="NO_STORY_IN_YOUR_DRAFT_SECTION">No available story in your draft section.</string>
    <string name="COPYRIGHT_ISSUE">Copyright issue</string>
    <string name="GARBAGE_CONTANT">Garbage content and unrelated to connecting thoughts</string>
    <string name="INAPPROPRIATE_CONTENT">Inappropriate content</string>
    <string name="REPORT_EMAIL">Email *</string>
    <string name="REPORT_NAME">Name *</string>
    <string name="YOU_CAN_ENTER_YOUR_PROBLEM_HERE">Type your problem here....</string>
    <string name="REPORT_TO_STORY">Report to story</string>
    <string name="CHOOSE_LANGUAGE">Choose Language</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_CHOOSE_LANGUGE">Please choose language to proceed.</string>
    <string name="SAVE">Save</string>
    <string name="CHOOSE_YOUR_DESIRED_LANGUAGE">Select your language</string>
    <string name="ENTER_VELID_NUMBER">Please Enter Valid Number</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_ACCEPT_TERMS_AND_CONDITIOIN">Please accept Terms and condition.</string>
    <string name="PHONE_NUMBER">Phone No.</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_BE_PATIENT">please be patient, data is loading.</string>
    <string name="PHONE_NUMBER_REPORT">Phone No.*</string>
    <string name="OK">Ok</string>
    <string name="YOU_CAN_REPORT_FOR">You can report for</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_PROVIDE_YOUR_NAME">Please provide name</string>
    <string name="PROVIDE_YOUR_NUMBER">Please provide phone number</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_PROVIDE_EMAIL">Please provide email id</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_WRITE_ABOUT_YOUR_PROBLEM">Please mention your problem</string>
    <string name="WE_WILL_TAKE_ACTION">We will take appropriate action after examine your report.</string>
    <string name="Incomming_report">Incomming Report</string>
    <string name="REPORT_TYPE">Type of report</string>
    <string name="REPORTER_LIST">Report List</string>
    <string name="OPEN_STORY">Read Story</string>
    <string name="TAKE_ACTION">Take Action</string>
    <string name="REPORTED_BY">Reported By</string>
    <string name="SUSPEND_STORY">Suspend Story</string>
    <string name="IGRORE_REPORT">Ignore Report</string>
    <string name="TAKE_ACTION_AGAINST_REPORT">Take Action</string>
    <string name="DO_YOU_REALLY_WANT_TO_SUSPAND_STORY">Do you really want to suspend story ?</string>
    <string name="DO_YOU_REALLY_WANT_TO_REJCT_REPORT">Do you really want to declare this report as fake ?</string>
    <string name="STORY_UNPUBLISHED_SUCCESSFULLY">Story unpublished successfully.</string>
    <string name="SUBMITING_REPORT">Submitting Report</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_WAIT_WHILE_WE_SUBMIT_REPORT">Please wait while we submitting your report.</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_WAIT_WHILE_WE_UNPUBLISH_STORY">Please wait while we suspending story.</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_WAIT_WHILE_WE_REJECTING_REPORT">Please wait while we rejecting report.</string>
    <string name="REPORT_DECLARED_AS_FAKE">Report declared as fake.</string>
    <string name="NO_REPORT_YET">No report yet.</string>
    <string name="SHARE_WITH">Share with</string>
    <string name="SELECT_PICTURE">Select Picture</string>
    <string name="VERIFY">Verify</string>
    <string name="SEND_otp">Send OTP</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_ENTER_YOUR_NAME">Please enter your name so that people can identify you.</string>
    <string name="ENTER_NAME">Enter Name</string>
    <string name="SELECT_CHOOSE">Select Language</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_ENTER_YOUR_NAME_BEFORE_SAVING_IT">Enter your name before saving it.</string>
    <string name="FRIENDS">Friends</string>
    <string name="NOTIFICATION">Notification</string>
    <string name="SENT_A_CONNECTION_REQUEST">Wants to connect with you.</string>
    <string name="CLEAR_NOTIFICATION">Clear Notification</string>
    <string name="MIRACLE_OFFLINE_MESSAGE">Miracle just not happen by itself.
        Many people get buried for their one Miracle so that they can do something which can be said as miracle.
        Those who have the courage to be buried for their miracle.  one day they takes step towards miracles.   \n
                                        -------- By Connecting Thoughts Team</string>
    <string name="CHECK_OUT_CONNECTING_THOUGHTS">Check out connecting thoughts and meet people like you.</string>
    <string name="HIDE_YOUR_IDENTITY">Do you wanna hide your identity in this story ?</string>
    <string name="UNKNOWN">Unknown</string>
    <string name="SORRY_AUTHOR_OF_THIS_STORY_IS_UNKNOWN">Sorry Author of this story is unknown.</string>
    <string name="ABOUT_US">About Us</string>
    <string name="MY_profile">My Profile</string>
    <string name="BIRTH_DAY">Birth Day</string>
    <string name="gender">Gender</string>
    <string name="CLEAR_HISTORY">Clear History</string>
    <string name="CLEAR_LIBRARY">Clear Library</string>
    <string name="YOU_DID_NOT_READ_ANY_STORY_YET">You have not read any story yet.</string>
    <string name="HOW_TO_WRITE_IN_CONNECTING_THOUGHTS">How to write and publish?</string>
    <string name="HOW_TO_SEND_CONNECTION_REQUEST">How to send connection request?</string>
    <string name="HOW_ACCEPT_CONNECTION_REQUEST">How to accept connection request?</string>
    <string name="SEND_YOUR_FIRST_MESSAGE">How send your first message?</string>
    <string name="START_CONVERSATION">How start conversation?</string>
    <string name="ENTER_MOBILE_NO_TO_VERIFY">Enter mobile number to verify it.</string>
    <string name="VERIFY_PHONE_NO">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="I_ACCEPT">I accept </string>
    <string name="terms_and_condition_action_btn">&#160; Terms &amp; Condition*</string>
    <string name="FOR_ANY_KIND_OF_SUGGESTION_OR_PROBLEM">Want to suggest something for connecting thoughts?</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_INSTALL_GMAIL_TO_SEND">Please install gmail into your device</string>
    <string name="I_WANT_TO_SUGGEST_SOMETHING">I want to suggest</string>
    <string name="MY_SUGGESTIONS">My suggestions</string>


    <string name="WHAT_IS_PURPOSE_OF_CT_1">Connecting Thought is an online platform where people can write And publish their creation.</string>
    <string name="WHAT_IS_PURPOSE_OF_CT_2">The main objective of Connecting Thought is to provide people with a platform where people can share stories of their struggles,
        their successes, their accomplishments, their losses, their memories and their life experiences.</string>
    <string name="WHAT_IS_PURPOSE_OF_CT_3">In Connecting Thought, people meet people of the same type of thinking.</string>
    <string name="WHAT_IS_PURPOSE_OF_CT_4">If you want to help in any way to grow this community, then welcome to our team.</string>
    <string name="send_MAIL_TO_US">Send mail to us</string>
    <string name="WHAT_IS_PURPOSE_OF_CT_5">If you want to give us financial support, click on this button.</string>
    <string name="FINIANCIAL_SUPPORT">Financial support</string>
    <string name="I_WANT_TO_JOIN_CT">I want to join connecting thoughts</string>
    <string name="I_WANT_GROW_CT">I want to help this community</string>
    <string name="BECOME_A_PARTNER">Become a partner</string>
    <string name="HOW_MUCH_YOU_WANT_TO_HELP">Enter Amount</string>
    <string name="Proceed">Proceed</string>
    <string name="ENTER_AMOUNT">Enter Donation Amount</string>
    <string name="Donation">Donation</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_ENTER_DONATION_AMOUNT">Please enter donation amount more then zero</string>
    <string name="terms_and_condition_action">Terms &amp; condition</string>
    <string name="PRIVECY_POLICY">Privacy policy</string>
    <string name="OR">Or sign in with Google</string>
    <string name="UPDATE">Update</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_AVILABELE">Update Available</string>
    <string name="NEW_UPDATE_AVILABLE">Hi friends, we know that you are in a hurry but you need to update this
        app so that you can get a better experience of this app.</string>
    <string name="READ_SETTING">Read setting</string>
    <string name="SORRY_TEXT_SIZE_NOT_DECREASES">Text size can not decreases beyond this size.</string>
    <string name="SORRY_TEXT_SIZE_NOT_INCREASES">Text size can not increase beyond this size.</string>
    <string name="LOADING_USER_DATA">Please wait while we load user data</string>
    <string name="WRITE_YOUR_MESSAGE">Write your message</string>

    <string name="TERMS_AND_CONDITION">Terms and condition</string>
    <string name="PRIVACY_POLICY">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="ABOUT_US_CONNECTING_THOUGHTS">About Connecting Thoughts</string>
    <string name="ABOUT_CONNECTING_THOUGHTS">We are heighly dedicated team</string>

    <string name="LOAD_MORE_COMMENT">LOAD ALL COMMENTS</string>
    <string name="CONNECTING_THOUGHTS_PROMO">Connecting Thoughts Promo</string>
    <string name="GO_TO_HELP">Go to help</string>
    <string name="DO_YOU_WANT_SOME_HELP">Do you want some help ?</string>
    <string name="GO_TO_HELP_MESSAGE">If you are facing any kind of problem in Connecting Thoughts,
        you can go to help seciton of Connecting Thoughts.</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_GIVE_PERMISSIONS_FOR_IMAGE_MESSAGE">Need a permission to access multimedia files.</string>
    <string name="ONLY_IMAGE_FILE_IS_SUPPORTED">Sorry, only image file supported</string>
    <string name="OPEN_AUTHOR_DETAIL">Story Author Detail</string>
    <string name="AUTHOR_DETAIL">Author Detail</string>
    <string name="NO_NEW_CONNECTION_REQUEST">No new connection request</string>
    <string name="YOU_HAVE_NOT_STARTED_ANY_CONVERSATION_YET">You have not started any conversation yet.</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_RATE_FIRST">Please rate first</string>
    <string name="GOOGLE_AUTH_FAILED">Google authentication is failed, please try again with another account.</string>


</resources>
